Guide to the School of Forestry and Environmental Studies, Yale University, Records of the Dean
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Records of George A. Garratt, 1945-1969; Accession 1982-A-015
  - H
    - 1946-1955 (Box 13, Folder 157-158)
    - 1955-1963 (Box 14, Folder 159-161)
  - Honorary Degrees, Committee on, 1958 (Box 20, Folder 252)
  - Housing and Apartments for Students, 1962 (Box 20, Folder 253)
  - I
    - 1946-1955 (Box 20, Folder 255-256)
    - 1955-1963 (Box 21, Folder 257-259)
  - Industrial Forestry-Professorship, 1954-1962 (Box 21, Folder 260)
  - Industrial Forestry Seminar
    - 18th-Announcements and Agendae, 1961 (Box 21, Folder 261)
    - 19th-St. Paul Minnesota-Announcements and Agendae, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 262)
    - 20th-New Haven, CT-Announcements and Agendae, 1962 (Box 21, Folder 263)
    - 2lst-Berkeley, CA, 1963 (Box 21, Folder 264)
    - 22nd-Toronto, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 265)
    - 23rd-Announcements and Agendae, 1964 (Box 21, Folder 266)
    - General Study of, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 267)
    - 1953-1956 (Box 21, Folder 268-269)
    - 1956-1958 (Box 22, Folder 270-271)
    - Proceedings, 1955-1960 (Box 22, Folder 272-273)
  - Inventory, 1952 (Box 22, Folder 274)
  - J, 1946-1963 (Box 22, Folder 275-279)
  - K, 1946-1950 (Box 22, Folder 280-284)
  - L
    - 1946-1950 (Box 22, Folder 285)
    - 1950-1963 (Box 23, Folder 286-289)
  - Land Extension-plans, undated (Box 23, Folder 290)
  - Library-Yale Forestry School, 1961 (Box 23, Folder 291-292)
  - Library-Yale Forestry School-Position Classification and Pay Plan, 1949 (Box 23, Folder 293)
  - Logging (See: Mergen, folder 26), 1965-1966
  - M
    - 1946-1961 (Box 23, Folder 295-299)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 24, Folder 300)
  - Mc
    - 1946-1950 (Box 24, Folder 301)
    - 1956-1958 (Box 24, Folder 302)
  - Maine, University of-Curriculum in Forestry, 1960-1962 (Box 24, Folder 303)
  - N, 1946-1963 (Box 24, Folder 305-311)
  - National Academy of Sciences-National Research Council, 1963-1965 (Box 24, Folder 312)
  - National Science Foundation
    - Correspondence, 1961-1965 (Box 25, Folder 313)
    - Environmental Biology Program (See: Faculty Research, 40-41), 1963-1969
    - Grant Proposals Rejected (See: Faculty Research, 44), 1961-1966
  - Naval Research: Correspondence etc., 1947-1948 (Box 25, Folder 314)
  - Naval Research Project
    - Contract NONR609 (13)
      - 1948-1950 (Box 25, Folder 315)
      - 1955-1963 (Box 25, Folder 316-319)
      - Progress Reports (first 2 of 5), 1958-1963 (Box 25, Folder 320-321)
      - Progress Reports (last 3 of 5\), 1958-1963 (Box 26, Folder 322-324)
    - Final Report, 1957-1958 (Box 26, Folder 325)
    - Financial Statements
      - Non-Faculty Employment, 1947-1958 (Box 26, Folder 326)
      - Salaries and Wages, 1957-1950 (Box 26, Folder 327)
      - University Statements of Account (Box 26, Folder 328)
    - Financial Status Reports, circa1947-1955 (Box 26, Folder 329)
    - Investigation, Republic of Panama-W.L. Stern, 1955-1958 (Box 26, Folder 330)
    - Monthly Reports of Personnel, 1950-1959 (Box 27, Folder 331)
    - Properties of Tropical Wood, 1948-1953 (Box 27, Folder 334-338)
    - SAR/N70NR-28810, 1953-1956 (Box 28, Folder 339-340)
  - New England Council, circa1955 (Box 28, Folder 341-342)
  - News Releases, 1946-1963 (Box 28, Folder 343-348)
  - Northeast Forestry Experiment Station, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 349)
  - Norway Fellowship for Forestry Studies, 1951-1952 (Box 29, Folder 350)
  - O
    - 1950-1955 (Box 29, Folder 351-352)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 29, Folder 353)
  - Oastler Lecture Series, 1963-1965 (Box 29, Folder 355)
  - Organization for European Economic Cooperation, 1951 (Box 29, Folder 356)
  - P, 1946-1963 (Box 29, Folder 357-360)
  - Pack, Charles Lathrop, Prize
    - 1956 (Box 29, Folder 361)
    - Announcement, undated (Box 29, Folder 362)
  - Personnel Office
    - 1945-1964 (Box 29, Folder 363-364)
    - Memoranda of Employment, 1950-1951 (Box 29, Folder 365)
  - President"s Office, 1945-1954 (Box 29, Folder 366-367)
  - President"s Office, Yale University, 1956-1958 (Box 29, Folder 368)
  - President"s Reports, 1950-1965 (Box 30, Folder 369)
  - Protexol Corporation vs. Koppers Company (Box 30, Folder 370)
  - Provost"s Office
    - 1946-1950 (Box 30, Folder 371)
    - 1955-1958 (Box 30, Folder 372)
  - Purchases, Bureau of Correspondence, 1950-1961 (Box 30, Folder 373-376)
  - R, 1946-1963 (Box 30, Folder 377-380)
  - Recruitment in Canada, circa1961 (Box 30, Folder 381)
  - Recruitment in Central States, circa1961 (Box 30, Folder 382)
  - Recruitment in the Midwest, circa1961 (Box 30, Folder 383)
  - Recruitment in the Northeast, circa1961 (Box 30, Folder 384)
  - Recruitment in the Northwest, circa1961 (Box 31, Folder 385)
  - Recruitment in the Southeast, circa1961 (Box 31, Folder 386)
  - Recruitment in the Southwest-California, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 387)
  - Recruitment of Students-General File, 1960-1961 (Box 31, Folder 388)
  - Registrar"s Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 31, Folder 389)
  - Rensselaer-Wardwell Bartram Memorial Scholarships, 1955-1957 (Box 31, Folder 390)
  - Rockefeller, James S.-Gift to Forestry School, 1956 (Box 31, Folder 392)
  - Rutgers University-Policy regarding Admission of Graduates, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 393)
  - S, 1946-1962 (Box 31, Folder 394-398)
  - Sage Hall
    - Inventories, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 399)
    - Parking, 1947-1954 (Box 32, Folder 400)
  - Salary Scale of Staff, 1946-1947, 1954 (Box 32, Folder 401)
  - Scholarships-Timber Engineering Company, 1949-1958 (Box 32, Folder 402)
  - Scholarships and Awards, 1956-1958 (Box 32, Folder 403-404)
  - Scholarships and Awards-Scott Paper Company-Gilbery Kinney Award, 1954-1961 (Box 32, Folder 405-406)
  - Scholarships and Fellowships
    - Offers of Various Institutions, 1950-1961 (Box 32, Folder 407-409)
    - Announcements of Yale School of Forestry (See: Mergen, 302), 1963-1968
    - Scott Paper Co. Foundation Fellowship, 1962-1964 (Box 32, Folder 410)
    - Weyerhauser Foundation Fellowship for Graduate Study, 1964 (Box 32, Folder 411)
  - Scholarship and Loan Awards, 1940-1948 (Box 32, Folder 412-413)
  - Scholarships and Loans
    - 1952-1956 (Box 32, Folder 414)
    - 1960-1961 (Box 32, Folder 415)
  - Secretary"s Office, 1945-1958 (Box 33, Folder 416-418)
  - Service Bureau-Repairs etc., 1945-1958 (Box 33, Folder 419-421)
  - Sheffield Scientific School, 1945-1950 (Box 33, Folder 422)
  - Southeastern Forestry Equipment Station, 1955 (Box 33, Folder 423)
  - Spring Camp-Crossit, Arkansas, 1962-1966 (Box 33, Folder 424)
  - Stanford Research Institute-Research Survey on Forest Products, 1956 (Box 33, Folder 425)
  - Summer Activities Office and Registration, 1964-1965 (Box 33, Folder 427)
  - Summer Camp, Norfolk, CT, 1960-1966 (Box 33, Folder 428-429)
  - Summer Employment-Students, 1962-1965 (Box 34, Folder 430)
  - T
    - 1945-1958 (Box 34, Folder 431-432)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 34, Folder 433)
  - "Timbers of the New World"-Related Correspondence, Royalty Statements, 1947-1961 (Box 34, Folder 434)
  - Treasurer's Office
    - Correspondence
      - 1945-1956 (Box 34, Folder 435-438)
      - 1957-1958 (Box 35, Folder 439)
    - Memoranda of Gifts, 1952-1958 (Box 35, Folder 440-441)
    - Memoranda of Gifts-Henry S. Graves Memorial, 1952-1955 (Box 35, Folder 442)
    - Monthly Statements
      - 1945-1952 (Box 35, Folder 443-444)
      - 1955-1958 (Box 35, Folder 445)
    - Remittance Slips, 1955-1958 (Box 35, Folder 446)
  - Tropical Forestry, 1951-1955 (Box 35, Folder 447)
  - Tropical Woods
    - Financial (Box 35, Folder 448)
    - General Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 449)
    - Memoranda of Agreement (See: Mergen, 329), 1964-1965
    - University Microfilms, Catalogue of Back Issues (See: Mergen, 330), 1961-1966
  - Truck for Field Work, 1945-1954 (Box 35, Folder 451)
  - U, 1945-1962 (Box 35, Folder 452-454)
  - Undergraduate Affairs-a report, circa1953 (Box 35, Folder 455)
  - Undergraduate Preparation, 1945-1953 (Box 35, Folder 456)
  - Undergraduate Registration for Forestry Courses, 1960 (Box 35, Folder 457)
  - Union Bay-Camp Paper Corporation
    - White, Z.B., Reports on Tree Plantings, 1960-1962 (Box 35, Folder 458)
    - Review of Forest Management Practices, 1962 (Box 36, Folder 459-460)
  - United Nations, Food and Agricultural Organization, 1947-1953 (Box 36, Folder 461)
  - United States Forest Service
    - "Biochemistry of Wood Deterioration"-Cowling, 1964 (Box 36, Folder 462)
    - Industrial Management Research Agreement, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 463)
    - Memorandum of Agreement; Hanson, Lowe, 1963 (Box 36, Folder 464)
    - Northeastern Forestry Experiment Station (See: Faculty Research, 102), 1957-1971
  - University Council
    - 1949-1955 (Box 36, Folder 465-469)
    - 1956-1961 (Box 37, Folder 470-474)
    - Committee on School of Forestry-Report on Answer to Questionnaire, 1950 (Box 37, Folder 475)
    - Questionnaires and Answers, 1950-1952 (Box 38, Folder 476)
    - Reports etc., undated (Box 38, Folder 477)
    - Reports etc., 1950-1952 (Box 38, Folder 478-480)
  - University Health-Department of, Circa 1950-1960 (Box 38, Folder 481-483)
  - V
    - 1945-1957 (Box 38, Folder 484-486)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 38, Folder 487)
  - W
    - 1945-1958 (Box 39, Folder 488-491)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 39, Folder 492)
  - Water Resources Management Proposal, 1953-1954 (Box 39, Folder 493)
  - Wildlife Ecology (See: Mergen, Folder 42), 1965
  - Wood Products Research Society, 1957-1958 (Box 39, Folder 496)
  - Wood Technology Research Society, 1957-1958 (Box 39, Folder 497)
  - Woolsey, Theodore-"Studies in French Forestry", undated (Box 39, Folder 498)
  - World Forestry Congress (5th), 1959-1961 (Box 39, Folder 499)
  - Y
    - 1945-1950 (Box 40, Folder 500)
    - 1955-1958 (Box 40, Folder 501)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 40, Folder 502)
  - Yale-Inter-office correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 40, Folder 503)
  - Yale-Miscellaneous correspondence, 1961-1965 (Box 40, Folder 504)
  - Yale Alumni Fund, 1961-1962 (Box 40, Folder 505-506)
  - Yale Forestry School Alumni-Class of 1900-Fiftieth Reunion, 1950 (Box 40, Folder 507)
  - Yale Forestry School Alumni Association
    - Bank Statements, 1958-1959 (Box 40, Folder 508)
    - Business Correspondence, 1958-1960 (Box 40, Folder 509)
    - Clerical Bureau, 1958 (Box 40, Folder 510)
    - Executive Council
      - 1947-1949 (Box 40, Folder 511)
      - 1950-1956 (Box 41, Folder 512-513)
    - News, 1945-1958 (Box 41, Folder 514)
    - News, Notes, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 515)
    - Treasurer"s Reports (Box 41, Folder 516)
  - Yale Forestry School Alumni Council, 1958-1962 (Box 41, Folder 517)
  - Yale Forestry School Alumni Fund
    - 1958-1962 (Box 41, Folder 518-519)
    - Correspondence, 1959-1962 (Box 41, Folder 520-521)
    - Total Sheets, 1960 (Box 41, Folder 522)
  - Yale Forestry School Collections, Circa 1955 (Box 41, Folder 523)
  - Yale Forestry School Financial Campaign
    - 1952-1956 (Box 42, Folder 524-527)
    - Solicitation Information, 1955-1958 (Box 42, Folder 528-529)
  - Yale Forestry School Library, Circa 1950-1960 (Box 42, Folder 530)
  - Yale Health Plan and Health Center (Box 42, Folder 531)
  - Yale Medal, 1958 (Box 42, Folder 532)
  - Yale Natural Preserve
    - Committee Meetings (See: Mergen, 389), 1955-1966
    - Correspondence (See: Mergen, 390-391), 1953-1967
    - Expenditures (Box 42, Folder 533)
    - Status of, 1953-1954 (Box 42, Folder 534)
  - Yale University Press Correspondence-"Timbers of the New World", 1963 (Box 43, Folder 535)
  - Z
    - 1945-1958 (Box 43, Folder 536-538)
    - 1961-1963 (Box 43, Folder 539)
  - RESTRICTED MATERIAL
    Restricted until Jan 1, 2040.
    - Chinese Students-Correspondence and Transcripts, 1945-1946 (Box 43, Folder 541-543)
    - Faculty: Yale Forestry School
      - App1icants and Correspondence, 1953 (Box 44, Folder 544)
      - Applicants Seriously Considered, 1953-1954 (Box 44, Folder 545)
      - Applications for staff of Yale Forestry School (Box 44, Folder 546)
      - Lumbering Instruction: prospects, 1952 (Box 44, Folder 547)
      - Professorship in Industrial Forestry, 1953-1954 (Box 44, Folder 548-549)
      - Staff Vacancy in Wood Anatomy and Tropical Forestry, 1952-1953 (Box 44, Folder 550)
    - Faculty Committee on the Forest Service Curriculum, 1953-1963 (Box 44, Folder 551)
    - Faculty Position: Ecology-Background and List of Candidates, 1964 (Box 44, Folder 552)
    - Faculty Position: Ecology-Returns from First Round of Letters, 1964 (Box 45, Folder 553)
    - Faculty Position(s)
      - Forest Management Candidates, 1962-1963 (Box 45, Folder 554)
      - Forest Management Vacancy Announcement and Nomination, 1962 (Box 45, Folder 555)
      - Forest Pathology
        - 1957-1960 (Box 45, Folder 556-557)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 45, Folder 558)
      - Candidates Files, 1960 (Box 45, Folder 559-560)
      - Sources and Suggestions, 1962-1964 (Box 46, Folder 561-562)
      - Wildlife Ecology, 1964 (Box 46, Folder 563)
      - Wood Anatomy
        - Correspondence File, 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 564)
        - 1959-1960 (Box 46, Folder 565)
        - No date (Box 46, Folder 566-567)
      - Miscellaneous Inquiries, 1959-1962 (Box 46, Folder 568)
    - Student Appraisals and Junior Forestry Exam, 1950-1951 (Box 46, Folder 569)
    - Student Appraisals, Circa 1951, 1955 (Box 47, Folder 570)
    - Students-Ranking According to Grades, 1946-1949 (Box 47, Folder 571)
    - Yale Corporation Votes (Staff Positions), 1945-1958 (Box 47, Folder 572)
- Records of Francois Mergen, 1962-1977; Accession 1982-A-018
  Restricted until Jan 1, 2013.
  - Subject/Correspondence files, 1962-1977, Series I
    - A Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Activities of the Dean, 1963-1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Ad Hoc Committee
      - "Dana Report", 1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
      - Faculty and Committee Report, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 5)
      - School of Forestry, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Advanced Management: North Carolina Project, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 6a)
    - Advertisements and Announcements, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Advisory Board of Plant Scientists - International Textbook Company, 1970-1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Alumni Association, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Alumni Board - Yale, 1966-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10-11)
    - Alumni Board - Yale Association of Class Officers, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 12)
    - Alumni - General Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 2, Folder 13)
    - Alumni, Personal Correspondence of Dean and, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 14)
    - Alumni Employment Questionnaire, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 15)
    - Alumni Fund, Yale Forestry School and Yale Alumni Fund, 1966-1970 (Box 2, Folder 16-17)
    - Alumni Magazine - Contributors, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 18)
    - Alumni - Positions Available - Men Recommended, 1965-1967 (Box 2, Folder 19)
    - Alumni Seeking Employment, 1965-1966 (Box 2, Folder 20)
    - American Foresters, Society of
      - Correspondence, 1966-1971 (Box 2, Folder 21-23)
      - New England Section - 50th Anniversary Meeting, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 24)
      - Visiting Scientists Program, 1965-1972 (Box 3, Folder 25)
      - SAF-NRC National Symposium, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 26)
      - National Symposium for Continuing Education for Foresters, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - American Forestry Association
      - 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 28)
      - Trailriders of the Wilderness, 1969-1974 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Association of Yale Alumni, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 30-32)
    - Association of Yale Alumni (Voigt), 1975 (Box 3, Folder 32a)
    - B Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 33-34)
    - Biology Department, 1966-1970 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Biology Editors, Council of, 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Biometerology, Committee on, 1967-1973 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Brookhaven National Laboratory, 1969- (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Budget, 1965-1967 (Box 4, Folder 39-40)
    - Building and Space Allocation, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Buildings
      - Greeley Memorial Laboratory, 1966-1971 (Box 4, Folder 42)
      - Sage Hall, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Bulletins - Requests for Copies, etc., 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Bursar's Employment, 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 45-46)
    - Business Management, Department of, 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - C Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 4, Folder 48-50)
    - Calendar Revision - Fall, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Canadian National Parks - Today & Tomorrow - University of Calgary, 1968 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Project CEVAL, 1971 (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Coalition for a New University, Undated (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Chubb Fellow Program, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - College Work-Study Program, 1968-1971 (Box 5, Folder 58-63)
    - Commencement, 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 64-66)
    - Committee Assignments, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 67)
    - Comptroller's Office, 1966-1968 (Box 6, Folder 68)
    - Computer Center, 1965-1969 (Box 6, Folder 69)
    - Connecticut Agricugtural Experiment Station - Correspondence, 1965-1970 (Box 6, Folder 70)
    - Connecticut Garden and Flower Show, 1971-1972 (Box 6, Folder 71)
    - Connecticut Research Commission, 1968-1971 (Box 6, Folder 72)
    - Connecticut State Graduate Scholarships Program, 1965-1970 (Box 6, Folder 73)
    - Connecticut, State of - Natural Areas Advisory Commission, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 74)
    - Connecticut - State Plant Materials Committee, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 75)
    - Consultant's Report on Nelson Ranch, 1967 (Box 7, Folder 75a)
    - Continuing Education, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 76)
    - Crossett "Forms" - Crossett Lumber Company, Crossett, Arkansas, 1965 (Box 7, Folder 76a)
    - Curricula - Yale Forestry School, and Various Other Schools, 1965-1967 (Box 7, Folder 77)
    - Curriculum Revision Committee, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 78)
    - D Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 79)
    - "Dahl Report", 1972 (Box 7, Folder 80)
    - Danforth Committee on Interprofessional Education, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 81)
    - Dean's Personal Correspondence with President Brewster, 1965-1966 (Box 7, Folder 82)
    - Doctoral Program, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 83)
    - Doctoral Students, 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 84)
    - E Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 7, Folder 85)
    - "Ecological Principles" Symposium for Journalists, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 86)
    - "Ecology as a Guide to Social Change" - Symposium, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 87-87a)
    - Ecology Extension Course, 1970-1974 (Box 8, Folder 88-89)
    - Ecology Magazine, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 90)
    - Ecology, National Institute of, 1968-1969 (Box 8, Folder 91)
    - Edgewood Park - Rowing Course, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 92)
    - Eisenmenger, Robert, 1972-1977 (Box 8, Folder 93)
    - Employee Benefits, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 94)
    - Employment Opportunities, 1965-1967 (Box 8, Folder 95-96)
    - Employment Opportunities for Students, 1979 (Box 9, Folder 97)
    - Engineering and Applied Science, 1966-1970 (Box 9, Folder 98)
    - Enormous Room Advisory Board, 1966-1968 (Box 9, Folder 99)
    - Enrollment, 1968-1970 (Box 9, Folder 100-101)
    - Enrollment and Registration, 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 102)
    - Enviroment Quality Education Act, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 103)
    - Environmental Education Office: "A Team Approach to Environmental Education", 1971 (Box 9, Folder 104)
    - Environmental Education Proposal - Professor Samuel Crosby, 1972-1974 (Box 9, Folder 105)
    - Environmental Science - Miscellany, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 106)
    - Environmental Teach-in, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 107)
    - F Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 9, Folder 108)
    - Faculty - Mason Forest Land Use Chair, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 109)
    - Faculty Bibliographies, 1968 (Box 9, Folder 110)
    - Faculty Club, 1966-1971 (Box 9, Folder 111)
    - Faculty Committees:
      - Ad Hoc, 1969-1970 (Box 9, Folder 112)
      - Admissions and Financial Aid, 1967 (Box 9, Folder 113)
      - Cooperation of other Schools & Departments of University, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 114)
      - Degree and Academic Standing, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 115)
      - Departmenta1 Computer Administration, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 116)
      - Equipment, Ad Hoc Committee on, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 117)
      - Forest Ecology, Ad Hoc:, 1966-1967 (Box 9, Folder 118)
      - Human Ecology, course in, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 119)
      - Languages - Language Examinations, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 120)
      - Library, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 121)
      - Master of Forestry Degree, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 122)
      - MFS - Curriculum Revision, 1970 (Box 10, Folder 123)
      - Publications, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 124)
      - Resource Management Activities, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 125-126)
      - Safety, 1969 (Box 10, Folder 127)
      - School Forests, 1967-1970 (Box 10, Folder 128)
      - Seminar Program, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 129)
      - Socio-Economic Aspects of Forestry - Ad Hoc, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 130)
      - Socio-Economics, Circa1967 (Box 10, Folder 131)
      - Socio-Psychology, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 132)
      - Space, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 133)
      - Student Recruitment, 1966-1968 (Box 10, Folder 134)
      - Tropical Woods, Program in, 1966 (Box 10, Folder 135)
      - University Courses for Undergraduates, 1966-1969 (Box 10, Folder 136)
      - Wood Science, 1967 (Box 10, Folder 137)
    - Faculty: Curriculum - Changes Suggested, 1965 (Box 10, Folder 138)
    - Faculty Meetings, 1967-1973 (Box 10, Folder 139-144)
    - Faculty Memoranda, 1965-1972 (Box 11, Folder 145-154)
    - Faculty Memoranda, 1972-1976 (Box 12, Folder 155-158)
    - Faculty - News Releases etc., 1965-1959 (Box 12, Folder 159)
    - Faculty Travel, 1967-1974 (Box 12, Folder 160-165)
    - Financial Aid Office & Admissions, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 166)
    - Financial Assistance - External, 1967 (Box 12, Folder 167)
    - Forest History, Society of, Inc., 1965-1972 (Box 12, Folder 168)
    - Forest History Society, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 169-170)
    - Forest History Society, 1966-1969 (Box 13, Folder 171-175)
    - Forest Service, U.S., 1963-1970 (Box 13, Folder 175-176)
      - Translation Services, 1963-1969 (Box 13, Folder 177)
    - Forestry Club, 1957-1970 (Box 13, Folder 178)
    - Forestry School Executives, Council of, 1966-1970 (Box 13, Folder 179-181)
    - Forestry Seminar, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 182)
      - Correspondence with Seminar Speakers, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 183)
    - G Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 14, Folder 185)
    - Graduate Affiliate Program, 1969-1971 (Box 14, Folder 186)
    - Graduate-Professional Student Senate, 1968-1973 (Box 14, Folder 187)
    - Graduate School Agenda for Meetings, 1967-1970 (Box 14, Folder 188)
    - Graduate School - Dean Donald W. Taylor, 1965-1970 (Box 14, Folder 189)
    - Graduate School - Foreign Language Requirement, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 190)
    - Graduation - General, 1965-1966 (Box 14, Folder 191)
    - Graduation, 1966 (Box 14, Folder 192)
    - Graduation, 1967-1972 (Box 15, Folder 193-198)
    - Grant and Contract Administration, 1966-1970 (Box 15, Folder 199)
    - Grey Lumber: "Cruise Sheets", 1970 (Box 15, Folder 199a)
    - H Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 15, Folder 200)
    - Heads of Midwest Forestry Education and Research Programs - (HOMFERD), 1970 (Box 15, Folder 201)
    - Health Plan and Health Center, Yale, 1968 (Box 15, Folder 202)
    - Housing: Professional and Graduate, 1969 (Box 15, Folder 203)
    - I Correspondence, 1966-1970 (Box 15, Folder 204)
    - Income and Expense Projection - Budget Fund Drive, 1973-1975 (Box 16, Folder 205)
    - Inquiries by Prospective Students, 1966-1970 (Box 16, Folder 206-207)
    - Institute Of Man and Science, 1965-1972 (Box 16, Folder 208)
    - Inter-American Institute of Agricultural Sciences of the OAS, 1968-1969 (Box 16, Folder 209-210)
    - Interdisciplinary Environmental Program, 1966 (Box 16, Folder 211)